Here is my solution for
下面说说
this multi-layer neural network for
我如何使用多层神经网络
classifying handwritten digits from the MNIST dataset.
分类 MNIST 数据集中的手写数字
So, here I've defined our activation function like before, so,
像之前一样定义激活函数
again this is the sigmoid function and here I'm flattening the images.
这是 S 型函数 在这里扁平化图像
So, remember how to reshape your tensors.
还记得如何变形张量吧
So, here I'm using.view.
使用 .view
So, I'm just grabbing the batch size.
传入批次大小
So, images.shape.
images.shape()
The first element zero here,
第一个图像是 0
gives you the number of batches in your images tensor.
获得图像张量里的批次数量
So, I want to keep the number of batches the same,
我希望批次数量可以不变
but I want to flatten the rest of the dimensions.
但是我要扁平化其他维度
So, to do this, you actually can just put in negative one.
所以 可以在这里输入 -1
So, I could type in 784 here but a kind of
其实我也可以在这里输入 784
a shortcut way to do this is to put in negative one.
但是更简便的方式是输入 -1
So, basically what this does is it takes 64 as your batch size here and then when you
在这里传入批次大小 64
put a negative one it sees this and then it just chooses
当你在这里输入 -1 时
the appropriate size to get the total number of elements.
它将设定相应的大小 保持元素总数不变
So, it'll work out on its own that it needs to make the second dimension,
它将自己判断第二个维度必须是 784
784 so that the number of elements
这样的话 变形之后
after reshaping matches the number elements before reshaping.
元素的数量和变形之前的一样
So, this is just a kind of quick way to flatten
这样可以快速扁平化张量
a tensor without having to know what the second dimension used to be.
我们不需要知道第二个维度的大小是多少
Then here I'm just creating our weight and bias parameters.
在这里设置权重和偏差参数
So, we know that we want an input of 784 units and we want 256 hidden units.
我们希望有 784 个输入单元 256 个隐藏单元
So, our first weight matrix is going to be 784 by 256.
第一个权重矩阵将是 784 x 256
Then, we need a bias term for each of our hidden units.
每个隐藏单元都需要一个偏差项
So we have 256 bias terms here in b1.
因此 b1 中有 256 个偏差项
Then, for our second weight's going from the hidden layer to
第二个权重连接的是隐藏层和输出层
the output layer we want 256 inputs to 10 outputs.
我们希望有 256 个输入和 10 个输出
Then again 10 elements in our bias.
偏差是 10 个元素
Before we can do a matrix multiplication of our inputs with the first set of weights,
和之前一样 我们可以进行矩阵乘法运算
our first weight parameters,
将输入与第一组权重参数相乘
add in the bias terms and passes
加上偏差项
through our activation functions so that gives us the output of our hidden layer.
然后传入激活函数 得出隐藏层的输出
Then we can use that as the input to our output layer, and again,
然后将该输出当做输出层的输入
a matrix multiplication with a second set of weights and the second set of bias terms.
再次与第二组权重相乘并加上第二组偏差项
This gives us the output of our network. All right.
获得网络的输出好了
So, if we look at the output of this network,
来看下网络的输出
we see that we get those 64.
有 64 行
So, first let me print the shape just to make sure we did that right.
先输出形状 确保操作正确
So, 64 rows for one of each of our sort of input examples and then 10 values,
有 64 行 表示 64 个输入样本 然后是 10 个值
so, basically it's a value that's trying to
这个值表示
say this image belongs to this class like this digit.
图像属于这个类别/数字
So, we can inspect our output tensor and see what's going on here.
我们查看下输出张量
So, we see these values are just sort of all over the place.
有大量的值
So, you got like six and negative 11 and so on.
6 -11 等等
But we really want is we want our network to kind of tell
但是我们希望给定某个图像后
us the probability of our different classes given some image.
网络能告诉我们图像属于各个类别的概率是多少
So, kind of we want to pass in an image to our network and then the output should be
如果我们向网络中传入图像
a probability distribution that tells us which are
输出应该是一个概率分布
the most likely classes or digits that belong to this image.
告诉我们图像最有可能属于哪个类别/数字
So, if it's the image of a six,
如果图像是 6
then we want a probability distribution where most of
那么输出应该是一个概率分布
the probability is in the sixth class.
最高的概率是第六个类别
So, it's telling us that it's a number six.
告诉我们它是数字 6
So, we want it to look something like this.
我们希望网络的判断是
This is like a class probability.
基于每个类别的概率
So, it's telling us the probabilities of
给定传入的图像后
the different classes given this image that we're passing in.
该图像属于不同类别的概率是多少
So, you can see that the probability for
可以看出
each of these different classes is roughly the same,
每个类别的概率大致相同
and so it's a uniform distribution.
因此是一个均匀分布
This represents an untrained network,
表明网络没有经过训练
so it's a uniform probability distribution.
所以是均匀概率分布
It's because it hasn't seen any data yet,
这是因为网络尚未见过任何数据
so it hasn't learned anything about these images.
还没有学习关于这些图像的任何规律
So, whenever you give an image to it,
即使你传入一个图像  无论传入的图像是什么
it doesn't know what it is so it's just going to give an equal probability to each class,
它都不知道图像是什么
regardless of the image that you pass in.
只是给出每个类别概率相等的分布
So, what we want is we want the output of our network to be
我们希望网络的输出
a probability distribution that gives us the probability
是一个概率分布
that the image belongs to any one of our classes.
告诉我们图像属于任何一个类别的概率
So for this, we use the softmax function.
所以 我们将使用 softmax 函数
So what this looks like is the exponential.
这是指数函数
So,you pass in your 10 values.
传入 10 个值
So, for each of those values,
对于每个值
we calculate the exponential of that value divided by
我们都使该值的指数
the sum of exponentials of all the values.
除以所有值的指数之和
So, what this does is it actually kind of squishes each
该函数的作用是
of the input values x between zero and one,
将输入值 x 压缩到 0 和 1 之间
and then also normalizes all the values so that
然后标准化所有值
the sum of each of the probabilities is one.
使概率之和为 1
So, the entire thing sums up to one.
即所有值相加为 1
So, this gives you a proper probability distribution.
这样就获得了我们想要的概率和为1的概率分布
What I want you to do here is actually implement
下面你的任务是
a function called softmax that performs this calculation.
实现这个 softmax 函数并完成这一计算过程
So, what you're going to be doing is taking the output from
即获取这个简单神经网络的输出
this simple neural network and has shaped 64 by 10 and pass it through
形状为 64 x 10
a dysfunction softmax and make sure it calculates
将其传入函数 softmax 中
the probability distribution for each of the different examples that we passed in.
确保对于传入的每个样本
Right? Good luck.
它都会计算样本的概率分布加油！